sgcarmart.com 2018-10-01

# Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement

SGCM Pte Ltd ('SGCM') respects the privacy of its users and will ensure compliance by its staff to the strictest standards of security and confidentiality in respect of all personal information and data submitted by its users. This Privacy Statement forms part of the Website Terms and Conditions of Use that can be found at http://www.sgcarmart.com/main/tos.php.

Purpose of Collection of Personal Data

When using www.sgcarmart.com ('the Website'), users may disclose or be asked to provide personal information and/or data. It may be necessary for users to provide SGCM with their personal information and/or data in order to have the full benefit of and to enjoy the various services on the Website. Although users are not obliged to provide the information and/or data as requested on the Website, SGCM will not be able to render certain services on the Website that depends on the personal information and/or data in the event that users do not provide the said information and/or data.

SGCM's purposes for collecting the information and data on the Website include the following:

  * (a) to assist users in finding the appropriate vehicle that they are looking for;
  * (b) to assist users in finding the appropriate accessories for their vehicles;
  * (c) to provide users with various services offered by the Website, and newsletters, information on vehicles, and promotional and marketing materials;
  * (d) to handle and follow up on users' enquiries and complaints;
  * (e) to contact users regarding administrative notices and communications relevant to his/her use of the Website and to respond to users' enquiries or requests;
  * (f) to assist SGCM with developments for future marketing and promotions;
  * (g) to personalise the advertising and content for the user;
  * (h) to verify the identity of each user; and
  * (i) to obtain statistics about users to analyse usage of the Website in order to improve and enhance the Website.

Collection of Personal Data

SGCM collects only the personal information that you choose to submit to us as well as information which is obtained from your browser. Such identifiable information may include your Name, Car Registration number, Contact Number, Address, E-mail address, Gender, Occupation, Industry and Personal Interests. Once you register with us and sign in to the Website, you are anonymous to us. We may also contact you from time to time to update your personal information to ensure that it is accurate and current.

Only duly authorised staff of SGCM will be permitted to access users' personal information and data, and SGCM will not release such personal information and data to any third parties except in the circumstances listed under the section "Disclosure of Data". 

Disclosure of Data

SGCM agrees to take all practicable steps to keep all personal information and data of users confidential and/or undisclosed, and will only disclose or transfer such information and data in accordance with this Statement. SGCM will only disclose and/or transfer users' personal information and/or data to SGCM's partners or affiliates who have made specific requests for such information and/or data, and will only do so with users' prior consent. However, SGCM may disclose and/or transfer such information and/or data to third parties without users' prior consent under the following circumstances:

  * (a) where the information and/or data is to be disclosed and/or transferred to any third party suppliers or service providers who have been duly authorized by SGCM to use such information and/or data and who will facilitate the services on the Website;
  * (b) where the information and/or data is to be disclosed and/or transferred to any agents, affiliates or associates of SGCM who have been duly authorized by SGCM to use such information and/or data;
  * (c) where such disclosure and/or transfer is necessary for SGCM to protect and defend its rights and property;
  * (d) where SGCM considers such disclosure and/or transfer necessary in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations, including without limitation compliance with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on SGCM; and/or
  * (e) where SGCM deems such disclosure and/or transfer necessary in order to maintain and/or improve the services on the Website.

By using the Website, users are deemed to have agreed to, consented to and authorized the disclosure and/or transfer of their personal information and data by SGCM in the circumstances stated above.

Subscription to Newsletters and Marketing Materials

SGCM may from time to time send newsletters and marketing materials to members of the Website based on the personal information and data that they have provided to SGCM. Such members will be able to "opt-out" of receiving such materials by logging in to their user account page on the Website and choosing to unsubscribe to the said materials.

Access to and Correction of Personal Data

Users are entitled to request access to or make amendments to their personal information and data kept with SGCM by contacting the [Personal Data Officer] at [admin@sgcarmart.com]. Alternatively, users may edit, amend or delete his/her personal information and data at any time by logging in to user account page on the Website. In the event that a user wishes to access or amend his/her personal information and data, SGCM may request him/her to provide personal details in order to verify his/her identity. SGCM will respond to a user's request within [30] days of his/her request and will endeavour to do so wherever possible, but SGCM may charge the user a reasonable fee for doing so

Cookies and Log Files

SGCM does not collect any personally identifiable information from any users whilst they visit and browse the Website. When users access the Website, SGCM records their visits only and does not collect their personal information or data. The Website's server software will also record the domain name server address and track the pages users visit and store such information in "cookies", and gather and store information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data, in log files. All these are done without users being aware that they are occurring. SGCM does not link the information and data automatically collected in the above manner to any personally identifiable information. SGCM generally uses such automatically collected information and data to estimate the audience size of the Website, gauge the popularity of various parts of the Website,   
measure users' traffic patterns and administer the Website. Such automatically collected information and data will not be disclosed save and except in accordance with the section entitled "Disclosure or Transfer of Data" (above).

SGCM also uses cookies from Google to serve ads on the Website. You may opt out of Google's cookies by visiting Google's page at this address [[http://www.google.com.sg/](https://www.google.com.sg/)]. 

Links to Other Sites

The Website may provide links to other websites which are not owned or controlled by SGCM. Personal information and data from users may be collected by third parties on these other websites when users visit such websites and make use of the services provided therein. Where and when users decide to click on any advertisement or hyperlink on the Website which grants users access to another website, the users' personal information and data which are deemed to be private and confidential may be exposed in these other websites. This Statement is only applicable to the Website. Users are reminded that this Statement grants no protection to users' personal information and data that may be exposed on websites other than the Website, and SGCM is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. Please refer to the privacy policies of such other websites before using those websites

Security

The security of users' personal information and data is important to SGCM. SGCM will always strive to ensure that users' personal information and data will be protected against unauthorized access. SGCM has implemented electronic and managerial measures which are, in its view, appropriate to safeguard, protect and secure users' personal information and data. All personal information and data provided by users are only accessible by the authorized personnel of SGCM or its authorized third parties, and such personnel shall be instructed to observe the terms of this Statement when accessing such personal information and data.

Users may rest assured that their personal information and data will only be kept for as long as is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which such personal information and data are collected. Regarding sensitive information, such as credit card numbers entered on SGCM's order forms, SGCM encrypts such information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). SGCM also uses a third party service provider to facilitate these electronic transactions on the Website.

SGCM follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and data submitted by users to the Website, both during transmission and once SGCM receives it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet,or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while SGCM strives to protect users' personal information and data against unauthorized access, SGCM cannot guarantee absolute security of such personal information and data. 

Retention of Personal Data

Once SGCM has obtained a user's personal information and/or data, such personal information and/or data will be maintained securely in SGCM's system. Subject to legal requirements and unless otherwise stated in this Statement, the personal information and/or data of users will be retained by SGCM until the purpose for which the personal information and/or data was collected is no longer being served by the retention of said personal information and/or data, and that retention is no longer necessary for legal or business purposes.

Users are still always entitled to erase their own personal information and/or data from SGCM’s database and to terminate his/her membership of the Website. 

Changes in this Privacy Statement

SGCM reserves the right to update, revise, modify or amend this Statement at any time as SGCM deems necessary without prior notice, and users are strongly advised to review this Statement frequently. If SGCM decides to update, revise, modify or amend this Statement, SGCM will post those changes to this webpage and/or other places as SGCM deems appropriate, so that users will be aware of what information SGCM collects, how SGCM uses it, and under what circumstances, if any, SGCM discloses it. If SGCM makes material changes to this Statement, SGCM will notify users on this webpage, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on the home page of SGCM.

Effective Date: 15-Jan-2013

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please fill up the feedback form from the Contact Us page.
